# **Muhammad Hanzala**

Karachi, Sindh • (+92) 324-0299256 • hanzala.m@outlook.com •

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/muhammad-hanzala-6a1a26332

Github: https://github.com/MalikHanzalaAsif

Portfolio: https://malikhanzalaasif.github.io/Portfolio/

**Full Stack MERN Developer** I am a Full Stack Developer with 2 years of experience in building web applications using the MERN stack. Skilled in both frontend and backend development. I enjoy working on user-friendly interfaces, solving coding challenges, and collaborating with teams to deliver quality projects.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Unique Advertisers • Gulberg Town Karachi • 10/2024 - Present

- Sole Full Stack Developer at a Service-based company. Handled end-to-end web development.
- Built and optimized business websites using MERN stack.improving performance and user engagement. Full Stack MERN Developer Full-time Contract

## Arc Inventador • Shahra-e-faisal karachi • 02/2024 - 08/2024

- Worked on real-world projects at a creative agency.
- Collaborated with teams of designers and backend developers and gained experience.
- Developed responsive UI components using React and Tailwind CSS, improving website aesthetics and performance. **Frontend Developer Internship**

#### **EDUCATION**

## CPISM, DISM in Web Development

Aptech Education • Tariq Road Karachi • 09/2023 - 09/2024

• Developed a Full Stack E-Project Web Application And collaborated with team members and designers to work in a fast paced environment.

## **Intermediate Pre Engineering**

Adamjee Govt Science College • Karachi

#### **SKILLS:**

- Frontend: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript/TypeScript, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, ReactJS.
- Backend: Node.js, Express.js.
- Database: MongoDB.
- Tools: Git, GitHub, DevOps.